A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor Joseph Johnson, 1852-1855
Library of Virginia
- Executive Papers of Governor Joseph Johnson, 1852-1855., Extent: 16 boxes. (Box 1-16)
  Governor Enoch L. Lowe, Maryland, asks for the delivery of various fugitives from justice in Virginia including Albert A. Bass charged with obtaining goods & merchandise under false pretences (1852 June 16); Jesse Coleman charged with larceny (1853 July 4); Henry Lehne charge with willful, malicious, & corrupt perjury (1853 Sept. 27); and Octavius McPherson Lyles charged with murder (1853 Dec. 14). Lowe also writes regarding the act of the Virginia General Assembly in relation to the North & South Railroad Company (1853 Mar. 5). Lastly, Lowe writes about the Virginia law concerning the holding of real estate by aliens, resident & non-resident (1853 Dec. 1). Governor Thomas W. Ligon, Lowe's successor, writes on 29 March 1854 regarding the running of the boundary line between Maryland & Virginia. On 20 April 1854, Ligon announces the appointment of George W. Hughes as commissioner on the part of Maryland to run the boundary line between Virginia & Maryland. Additionally, Ligon submits demands for fugitives including Jacob Grove & Thomas Kernan charged with larceny (1854 Mar. 27) and John H. Rhodes charged with horse stealing (1854 July 15). Governor William Bigler, Pennsylvania, also writes regarding the delivery of escaped convicts. Bigler requests the delivery of several fugitives including John H. Carroll charged with bastardy & fornication (1852 June 19); Dick O. Connell alias Keenan, a fugitive charged with larceny (1853 May 2); A. P. Hancer charged with obtaining goods under false pretences (1853 Aug. 3); William R. Cotton, Moses Roberts, charged with obtaining goods under false pretenses (1853 Sept. 23); Jacob Baker, charged with obtaining goods under false pretences (1853 Oct. 17, 1853 Nov. 7, & 1854 Jan. 19); Harrison Conley charged with obtaining goods under false pretenses (1854 Jan. 10); Leonard Wolf charged with fornication & bastardy (1854 Dec. 18); and Frank May charged with burglary (1855 May 3). In addition, Bigler writes as president of a convention of delegates appointed by the legislatures or governors of nine of the original thirteen states which assembled in Philadelphia for the purpose of considering the propriety of erecting some appropriate & durable memorial of the Declaration of Independence on the public grounds surrounding Independence Hall (1853 Mar. 1). Finally, Bigler transmits resolutions of the Pennsylvania Legislature relative to old soldiers (1854 Feb. 25). Bigler's successor, James Pollock, submits demands for Max Weigart charged with conspiracy to defraud (1855 Apr. 30); Henry Blauser, a fugitive accused of seduction, fornication, & bastardy (1855 Sept. 15); and Charles Redding charged with forgery & counterfeiting (1855 Dec. 21). Governor John Hubbard, Maine, issues his proclamation for a day of thanksgiving (1852 Sept. 3). Governor Reuben Wood, Ohio, issues a similar proclamation (1852 Oct. 18). Wood also writes demanding the delivery of George Roby charged with the crime of shooting with intent to kill (1852 Dec. 31) and the delivery of Thomas O. Jones who was charged with bigamy (1853 July 12). Wood's successor William Medill writes to request a day of thanksgiving (1853 Oct. 19) and to demand Briggs Martin, a fugitive from justice charged with feloniously assaulting & wounding with intent to ravish Barbarq Nettenger (1854 Sept. 12). Governor Horatio Seymour, New York, submits his demand for James H. Palmer, a fugitive from justice convicted of forgery (1853 Jan. 25). Seymour also demands James B. Dickerson who was charged with seduction (1853 Mar. 10). Secretary of State Elias W. Leavenworth, New York, requests information regarding the boundaries & county seats of Virginia for Messrs. Morse & Company of New York to publish a map of Virginia (1854 July 18). Leavenworth also writes regarding the support of humane institutions including asylums for the blind, insane, deaf, & dumb (1854 Aug. 23). Later, Governor Myron H. Clark, New York, demands Isaiah Broomfield, a free negro from New York imprisoned in a Goochland County jail (1855 July 4). William H. Ross, Delaware, writes regarding the Atlantic Railroad through Virginia, Maryland, & Delaware (1853 Mar. 16). Governor David S. Reid, North Carolina, encloses a requisition for Mack Wosborne who is confined in jail in Danville for stealing a horse (1853 Apr. 9). Governor Howell Cobb, Georgia, writes respecting the tax laws of Virginia appropriations to education, & state debt (1853 June 15). Governor Noah Martin, New Hampshire, writes regarding the delivery of John W. Rand, a fugitive charged with robbery & larceny (1853 Dec. 28). Governor John A. Winston, Alabama, writes regarding aid to the state to private railroad corporations (1854 Feb. 1). Oliver H. Perry, Secretary of State of Connecticut, encloses resolutions regarding the bill in Congress for the organization of the territories of Kansas & Nebraska (1854 May 18); Governor Lazarus W. Powell, Kentucky, requests the delivery of Thomas R. Robertson who stands charged with passing counterfeit money (1854 Oct. 30) and Hopson Binford, a fugitive charged with shooting Thomas James (1855 Aug. 28). Governor John H. Clifford, Massachusetts, writes regarding his refusal to submit to the demand of Governor Joseph Johnson for Richard H. Johnson, an alleged fugitive charged with feloniously, maliciously, & unlawfully beating & wounding John Gillis. Finally, Governor Henry J. Gardner, Massachusetts, asks for the arrest of Charles C. Toothaker charged with larceny (1855 Sept. 4).
  Additional significant correspondence includes the following: John Hayward, Boston, requesting information of Virginia counties & towns for the use of his Gazetteer of the United States (1852 Feb. 18); an anonymous letter, Washington, complaining about the block of stone presented by the state of Virginia for the Washington Monument (1852 Mar. 3); Joseph C. Cabell accepting his reappointment as visitor of the University of Virginia (1852 Apr. 12); John Ward, New York, encl. certificates of the United States Charge d' Affairs & Consul at Rome proving the completion by Thomas Crawford of two statues for the Washington Monument (1852 Oct. 15); G. R. P. James, British Consulate, Norfolk, re. promotion of commercial intercourse between Great Britain & Virginia (1853 Jan. 18); John M. Botts encl. a letter from a committee of citizens of New York presenting a bronze medal of Henry Clay (1853 Feb. 18); G. A. Myers, Thomas Giles, & W. H. Haxall, Committee of the Capitol Square, re. the failure of the Legislature to provide by law the completion of the improvement of Capitol Square in accordance with the plan of John Notman (1853 Apr. 22); Claudius Crozet re. the strike for higher wages by the hands employed in the tunnel for the Blue Ridge Railroad (1853 Apr. 19); Francis H. Smith, Superintendent of the Virginia Military Institute, transmitting a letter of a Committee of Cadets requesting the Armory Band for the commencement (1853 Apr. 19); Edward C. Marshall, President of the Manassas Gap Railroad Company, requesting arms to quell riots by Irish laborers (1853 June 27); William Whetten, Secretary of the Office of the Association for the Exhibition of the Industry of All Nations, N.Y., inviting the governor to the inaugural opening of the exhibition (1853 June 28); Theodore Sedgwick, President of the Office of the Association for the Exhibition of the Industry of All Nations in New York asking to be furnished with a state banner (1853 July 6); B. B. Minor re. the use of a small slip of ground between the Law Building & State Courthouse (incl. diagram) (1853 July 14); W. C. Horstmann & Sons, Philadelphia, re. a banner for the state of Virginia (incl. drawing) (1853 July 18); Henry A. Wise declining an appointment as treasurer (1853 July 27); Thomas J. Randolph resigning as visitor of the University of Virginia (1853 Sept. 29); J. Y. Mason resigning as visitor of the University of Virginia (1853 Nov. 8); members of the Legislature re. casts of Washington's Statue by Houdon to be deposited in the several collegiate institutions of the state (1854 Feb. 3); William J. Hubbard re. the cost of making & transporting casts of Houdon's statue in plaster (1854 Feb. 9); H. K. Ellyson, House of Delegates, re. the street proposed to be made by the City of Richmond through the Armory property (incl. minority report of the Armory Committee) (1854 Feb. 10); John Ward, N.Y. encl. certificates of the Directory of the Royal Academy of Plastic Arts at Munich re. the successful casting of the statue of Thomas Jefferson and the second bas relief for the Washington Monument at the request of Thomas Crawford (1854 Mar. 24); John Ward encl. a draft of Thomas Crawford on the state of Virginia for $15,000 and a certificate from the U.S. Consul at Rome of the completion of the Equestrian Statue of Washington (1854 June 23); Alexandre Vattemare, Paris, Agent of Virginia for International Exchange, encl. general regulations for the Universal Exhibition to be held in Paris in 1855 (1854 July 26); Alexandre Vattemare, re. a letter from Governor William Smith concerning payment for his expenses (1854 July 31); Alexandre Vattemare, Paris, re. exchanges of books (1854 Sept. 6); Francis T. Stribling re. directors for the Western Lunatic Asylum in Staunton (1854 Sept. 12); Charles Mason, Commissioner, U.S. Patent Office, requesting information relative to the drought (1854 Sept. 20); Robert E. Coxe, Charles L. Fleischmann, & Alexandre Vattemare, Committee appointed by the states of Alabama & New York as representatives at the Universal Exhibition to take place in Paris on 1 May 1855, re. regulations (1854 Oct. 9); Charles Dorwin, U.S. Consul at Montreal, encl. his business card & tendering his services in making collections in Canada (1854 Oct. 13); Henry S. Tanner, N.Y., complaining of the creation of a new map of Virginia which renders the copper plates in his possession worthless (1854 Nov. 13); Henry S. Tanner encl. an account for the storage, insurance, & transportation of thirteen copper plates used to make the map of Virginia (1854 Nov. 21); R. Archer proposing to purchase arms belonging to the state (1854 Nov. 29); Henry S. Tanner re. a new edition of the maps of Virginia he created twenty-five years ago (1854 Nov. 30); Powhatan Ellis, Jr., N.Y., encl. Tanner's receipt for four packages containing copper plates received from him (1854 Dec. 1); Robert King, Agent for T. B. Welch's portrait of Washington, transmitting an engraved copy of the portrait painted during the second term of the presidency of George Washington by Gilbert Charles Stuart for the Executive Mansion (1854 Dec. 6); Alexandre Vattemare, Paris, re. contributions by citizens of Virginia to the World's Fair of 1855 (1855 Jan. 13); Alfred Paul, French Consul, re. a set of maps to be presented to the state of Virginia (1855 Mar. 8); W. B. Davis, Wilmington, N.C., encl. a circular to the fifteen southern governors re. southern rights (1855 Apr. 14); Thomas Wallace, Petersburg, encl. the contract of R. A. Machen for building a gun house for the Petersburg Artillery (1855 June 20); John A. Washington proposing the sale of Mount Vernon to the state of Virginia (1855 June 18); Henry A. Wise resigning as visitor of the University of Virginia (1855 June 18); H. W. Herbert requesting stone from Capitol Square lying in the site of the old work shed (1855 Sept. 2); and Thomas Crawford, Rome, re. the bas relief for the Washington Equestrian Statue and the construction of the statue (1855 Oct. 29).
  Other noteworthy items include the following: a qualification of Joseph Johnson as governor (1852 Jan. 1); qualification of Willis P. Bocock as attorney general (1852 Jan. 22); proclamations of Governor Joseph Johnson offering rewards for the arrest of fugitives from justice (1852 Jan. 6, Feb. 2, 7, & 24, Mar. 20, June 12 16, & 28, Sept. 9, Nov. 27, Dec. 15; 1853 June 22, July 25, Aug. 17, 20, & 24, Dec. 3, 8, & 28; 1854 Jan. 9, 18, May 27, July 11 & 27; 1855 Mar. 8, Apr. 17, May 11, July 23, & Aug. 21), resolution of the General Assembly of Alabama for a ship canal across the peninsula of Florida (1852 Feb. 6); a joint resolution of the General Assembly of Indiana on the subject of the slave trade and colonization (1852 Mar. 8); report of the Committee of Claims on the appropriation of lands by Congress for Virginia land bounty claims (1852 Apr. 14); a proclamation of Governor Johnson for elections for circuit judges & judges of the Supreme Court of Appeals (1852 May 22); a proclamation of Governor Johnson for an election to supply the vacancy in Congress occasioned by the resignation of George W. Thompson (1852 Sept. 22); a proclamation for elections to supply the vacancies occasioned by the resignations of John Caddall as delegate to Pulaski County, Robert E. Scott as delegate to Fauquier County, & John A. Meredith as senator, & Conway Robinson as delegate of Richmond (1852 Sept. 22); a memorandum of agreement between the governor and R. Archer & Company (1852 Nov. 13); a proclamation of Governor Johnson for an election to supply the vacancy in the House of Delegates to supply the vacancy occasioned by the resignation of James W. Gray (1852 Nov. 18); a proclamation of Governor Johnson regarding the appointment of electors to choose a president & vice president of the United States (1852 Nov. 22); qualification of Charles S. Morgan as Superintendent of the Penitentiary (1852 Dec. 24); bond of Robert Johnston as auditor of public accounts (1852 Dec. 24); qualification of Stafford H. Parker as Register of the Land Office (1852 Dec. 30); qualification of Robert Johnston as Auditor of Public Accounts (1852 Dec. 31); a map of ground attached to the Navy Hospital at Norfolk proposed to be ceded to the United States government (1853 Jan. 31); a qualification of George W. Munford as Secretary of the Commonwealth (1853 Jan. 1); petition of William Hubard asking for the privilege of casting in plaster of Paris the entire Houdon Statue of Washington in the Capitol (1853 Feb. 17); a proclamation of Governor Joseph Johnson for an election in the General Assembly occasioned by the resignation of Charles Mason (1853 Apr. 15); a proclamation of Governor Johnson for the election of senators of the 1st class as required by the Constitution (1853 Apr. 22); a report of the Committee on the Capitol Square encl. a plan of the walks near the Capitol (1853 May 30); a proclamation of Governor Johnson designating the basement of the Methodist Episcopal Church in Warrenton as the place at which the circuit & county courts of Fauquier County be held until a new building is erected (1853 May 3); a proclamation of Governor Johnson for an election to supply the vacancy in the 14th Circuit occasioned by the death of Edward Johnston (1853 May 11); an agreement between E. S. Gay, paymaster of the Washington Monument, & Azel French for the rent of a parcel of land in Westham owned by the state (1853 June 18); a proclamation of Governor Johnson re. the election of commissioners of public works (1853 June 22); recommendations for the office of treasurer in place of Robert Butler, deceased (1853 July); a proclamation of Governor Johnson for an election to supply the vacancy in the 4th Circuit occasioned by the death of N. M. Taliaferro (1853 July 11); memorandum of agreement between Governor Johnson & Robert Edmond of Richmond for the lease of Union Warehouse in the town of Buchanan (1853 July 8); a proclamation of Governor Johnson for an election in Pittsylvania County to supply the vacancy in the House of Delegates occasioned by the resignation of George H. Gilmer (1853 Sept. 8); a deed between Governor Johnson & the United States for four parcels of land on the James River containing three acres each to be used for lighthouses, beacons, etc. (1853 Oct. 21); Governor's message & annual reports of the public officers of the state (1853 Dec. 5); petitions & correspondence for the pardon of John S. Mosby, a student at the University of Virginia, who was tried for maliciously & unlawfully shooting George R. Turpin (1853 Dec. 16); a report of the Directors of the Penitentiary regarding the escape of sundry convicts (1853 Dec. 30); petition of citizens of the United States in Paris asking that Congress will provide for the incorporation of the metrical decimal system into legislation of the U.S. (1854 Jan. 30); articles of agreement between Alexander Galt, Jr., & Governor Johnson for the completion of a statue of Thomas Jefferson (1854 Feb. 21); bond of George W. Clutter as auditor of Public Accounts (1854 Feb. 21); proceedings of the Rhode Island General Assembly reversing the decision of the courts in the case of Thomas W. Dorr charged with treason (1854 May 6); resolutions of Massachusetts re. officers, soldiers, & others who served in the War of 1812 (1854 May 8); bond of Alexander Galt for the execution of a marble statue of Thomas Jefferson (1854 July 10); proceedings of a courts martial held at the Armory for Peter Jackson, a private in the Public Guard charged with desertion (1854 Nov. 6); receipt of Henry S. Tanner for the storage of thirteen copper plates (1854 Nov. 21); payroll of officers & men of the 1st Virginia Volunteers ordered to protect property and guard prisoners at the Penitentiary on the occasion of the fire on the night of 7 December 1854 (1854 Dec. 16); qualification of J. B. Stovall as treasurer of the state (1854 Dec. 30); qualification of Stafford H. Parker as register of the Land Office (1854 Dec. 30); a contract between Charles Dimmock & George F. Maynard for leasing the Boring Mill (1855 Mar. 30); proceedings of the Board of Directors of the Penitentiary re. the appointment of Henry R. Jones as clerk (1855 June 19); and the Governor's Message & Reports of the Public Officers of the State of the Board of Directors and of the Visitors, Superintendents, & Other Agents of Public Institutions or Interests of Virginia (1855 Dec. 3).
  Arranged in chronological order.
  - 1852
    - January
      - 1-15 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 16-29 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - February
      - 2-15 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 16-28 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - March
      - 1-15 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 16-30 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - April
      - 1-15 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - 16-30 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - May
      - 1-10 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - 11-20 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - 21-31 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - June
      - 1-10 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - 11-20 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - 21-30 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - July
      - 1-15 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - 16-31 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - August
      - 2-15 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - 16-31 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - September
      - 1-15 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - 16-30 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - October
      - 1-15 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - 16-31 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - November
      - 1-15 (Box 3a, Folder 1)
      - 16-30 (Box 3a, Folder 2)
    - December
      - 1-15 (Box 3a, Folder 3)
      - 16-31 (Box 3a, Folder 4)
    - Undated. (Box 3a, Folder 5)
  - 1853
    - January
      - 1-15 (Box 3a, Folder 6)
      - 17-31 (Box 3a, Folder 7)
    - February
      - 1-15 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - 16-28 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - March
      - 1-15 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - 16-31 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - April
      - 1-12 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - 13-30 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - May
      - 1-15 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - 16-25 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - 26-31 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - June
      - 1-15 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - 16-30 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - July
      - 1-12 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - 13-23 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - 25-31 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - August
      - 1-15 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - 16-31 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - September
      - 1-15 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - 16-30 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - October
      - 1-15 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - 17-31 (Box 6a, Folder 1)
    - November
      - 1-15 (Box 6a, Folder 2)
      - 16-30 (Box 6a, Folder 3)
    - December
      - 1-10 (Box 6a, Folder 4)
      - 11-20 (Box 6a, Folder 5)
      - 21-31 (Box 6a, Folder 6)
    - Undated. (Box 6a, Folder 7)
  - 1854
    - January
      - 2-10 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - 11-17 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - 18-31 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - February
      - 1-15 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - 16-22 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - 23-28 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - March
      - 1-10 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - 11-20 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - 21-31 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - April
      - 1-15 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - 17-29 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - May
      - 1-10 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - 11-20 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - 22-31 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - June
      - 1-15 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - 16-30 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - July
      - 1-10 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - 11-21 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - 22-31 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - August
      - 1-15 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - 16-31 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - September
      - 1-15 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - 16-30 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - October
      - 1-14 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - 16-31 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - November
      - 1-15 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - 16-30 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - December
      - 1-15 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - 16-30 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 1855
    - January
      - 1-10 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - 11-20 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - 21-31 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - February
      - 1-15 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - 16-26 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - March
      - 1-15 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - 16-31 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - April
      - 2-15 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - 16-30 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - May
      - 1-15 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - 16-31 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - June
      - 1-10 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - 11-20 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - 21-30 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - July
      - 1-10 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - 11-20 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - 21-31 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - August
      - 1-15 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - 16-31 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - September
      - 1-15 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - 16-30 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - October
      - 1-10 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - 11-31 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - November
      - 1-15 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - 16-30 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - December
      - 2-15 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - 17-31 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Pardons
      - Dilworth, John (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Oversized (Clamshell Box)
  - 1852
    - Jan. 22 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Jan. 26 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - May 31 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Aug. 10 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Aug. 25 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 1853
    - May 30 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - July 18 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Aug. 29 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Dec. 28 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Dec. 30 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - 1854
    - Jan. 7 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Jan. 10 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - May 18 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - July 15 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Dec. 13 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - 1855
    - Oct. 11 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Nov. 1 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Oversized (Newspaper Box)
  - 1852
    - May 31 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Sept. 3 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Nov. 17 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Dec. 4 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 1853
    - May 2 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - May 6 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - May 26 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - May 26 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - May 26 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Aug. 8 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Aug. 17 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Nov. 19 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Nov. 19 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Dec. 28 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - 1854
    - Jan. 7 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Jan. 19 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Jan. 30 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Feb. 17 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Mar. 6 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Apr. 26 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Aug. 22 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Sept. 30 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Oct. 16 (Box 15, Folder 23)